YEVHEN MALYI

malyje164@gmail.com

+31687595983

Hilversum, XD 1213

SKILLS

- Employee Coaching and Motivation
- Administration and Reporting
- Front-End Programming: HTML5, CSS3
- Angular, React, Bootstrap, Materialize
- Object-Orient Programming (OOP)
- Version Control Systems: Git, GitHub
- JavaScript Libraries and Frameworks
- Node.js, MongoDB, Express.js API
- Back-End and Database Skills

EDUCATION

Zaporizhia National Technical University

Zaporozhye, Ukraine • 12/2014

Human Resources And Restaurant Business

Code Matrix Zone

Rotterdam, The Netherlands • 09/2022

Full Stack MERN Program

CERTIFICATIONS

 Code Matrix Master Training -06.2022-09.2022

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Hello, I have more than 15 years of experience in catering, I managed a large staff, made decisions in difficult situations, I can work in a team, create new projects, but now I want to find new experience, new knowledge. I want to change the type of activity, because in cooking I got stuck in a dead end and stopped developing. I am a fast learner, I am interested in my development in the IT field.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Clion group, Veladis, 'Fish & Chips'. - Senior Chef of the Cafe Chain and Acting Regional

Zaporozhye, Ukraine • 09/2019 - 07/2021
Controlled the work process of all cafes in my region, managed, trained staff, launched new projects of the company, integrated new products into the menu of the cafe network (the owners of the cafe network are the largest importer and production of fish products in Ukraine, created new dishes, kept documentation and etc.

Restaurant "Bella Vitta' - Senior Chef
Zaporozhye, Ukraine • 09/2018 - 08/2019
Created a new project, participated in the design and construction of a new restaurant. Created a production line, searched for and trained new personnel. Supervised the work of the restaurant after the opening.

HOBBY

Diving, hiking with a tent, spend time with family.

LANGUAGES

Dutch:	English:
Beginner (A1)	Elementary (A2)
Polish:	Russian:
Intermediate (B1)	Advanced (C1)